export const chapter = "Chapter - 9: The Secret of Casket";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "What was Ah-ling's initial plan regarding her wealth?",
          optionA: "She wanted to keep it for herself.",
          optionB: "She distributed it among her four sons.",
          optionC: "She donated it to a charity.",
          correctAnswer: "She distributed it among her four sons.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why did Ah-ling feel distressed after some time of living with her sons?",
          optionA: "She missed her old home.",
          optionB: "Her sons were not taking care of her.",
          optionC: "She had lost her wealth.",
          correctAnswer: "Her sons were not taking care of her.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Who offered Ah-ling a piece of advice to improve her situation?",
          optionA: "Her eldest son",
          optionB: "Her friend Jing-mei",
          optionC: "Her youngest son",
          correctAnswer: "Her friend Jing-mei",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What was the content of the ornamental chest Ah-ling brought home?",
          optionA: "Valuable gems",
          optionB: "Ordinary pebbles",
          optionC: "Money",
          correctAnswer: "Ordinary pebbles",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What change did Ah-ling notice in her sons and daughters-in-law after she obtained the casket?",
          optionA: "They started ignoring her.",
          optionB: "They became more caring and attentive.",
          optionC: "They became greedy for wealth.",
          correctAnswer: "They became more caring and attentive.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How long did Ah-ling stay with each of her sons as per her initial arrangement?",
          optionA: "Six months",
          optionB: "Three months",
          optionC: "One year",
          correctAnswer: "Three months",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why did Ah-ling never extend her stay with any of her sons?",
          optionA: "She didn't want to show favoritism.",
          optionB: "She preferred living alone.",
          optionC: "She had a personal reason.",
          correctAnswer: "She didn't want to show favoritism.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What did Ah-ling's friend Jing-mei give to her sons after Ah-ling's passing?",
          optionA: "A note with instructions",
          optionB: "The key to the casket",
          optionC: "A portion of Ah-ling's wealth",
          correctAnswer: "The key to the casket",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What did the casket actually contain when the sons opened it with the key?",
          optionA: "Valuable gems",
          optionB: "A heartfelt letter from their mother",
          optionC: "Ordinary pebbles",
          correctAnswer: "Ordinary pebbles",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What was the message in the note left by Ah-ling in the casket?",
          optionA: "Money is everything in life.",
          optionB: "True character is revealed by one's actions.",
          optionC: "Seek wealth above all else.",
          correctAnswer: "True character is revealed by one's actions.",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling distributed her entire wealth among her ________ sons.",
          optionA: "four",
          optionB: "two",
          optionC: "five",
          correctAnswer: "four",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling felt that her sons were becoming less and less ________ in welcoming her.",
          optionA: "generous",
          optionB: "cordial",
          optionC: "understanding",
          correctAnswer: "cordial",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's friend, Jing-mei, offered her a piece of advice to improve her ________.",
          optionA: "wealth",
          optionB: "situation",
          optionC: "health",
          correctAnswer: "situation",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When Ah-ling returned with the ornamental chest, her clothes were covered in ________.",
          optionA: "dust",
          optionB: "mud",
          optionC: "flowers",
          correctAnswer: "mud",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's sons tried to open the casket in her ________, but it was securely locked.",
          optionA: "presence",
          optionB: "absence",
          optionC: "sleep",
          correctAnswer: "absence",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling lived for ________ more years after the incident with the casket.",
          optionA: "three",
          optionB: "five",
          optionC: "nine",
          correctAnswer: "nine",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Jing-mei handed over the key to the casket to Ah-ling's ________ son.",
          optionA: "eldest",
          optionB: "youngest",
          optionC: "middle",
          correctAnswer: "eldest",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When the casket was opened, the contents were revealed to be ________.",
          optionA: "valuable gems",
          optionB: "ordinary pebbles",
          optionC: "gold coins",
          correctAnswer: "ordinary pebbles",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's message in the note emphasized the importance of one's ________.",
          optionA: "material wealth",
          optionB: "true character",
          optionC: "family ties",
          correctAnswer: "true character",
        },
        {
          question: "The text concludes with the arrival of ________.",
          optionA: "Amy's friend",
          optionB: "Amy's brother",
          optionC: "Amy's father",
          correctAnswer: "Amy's father",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling distributed her entire wealth among her four sons.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's sons were increasingly welcoming as time passed.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Ah-ling's friend, Jing-mei, offered her valuable advice.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The ornamental chest Ah-ling brought home was filled with valuable gems.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's sons successfully opened the casket in her absence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling lived for five more years after the incident with the casket.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Jing-mei handed over the key to the casket to Ah-ling's youngest son.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "When the casket was opened, it contained valuable gems.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Ah-ling's message in the note emphasized the importance of one's material wealth.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "The text concludes with the arrival of Amy's friend.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
